so i'm currently sitting here being a black radical creative while listening to how to go
mad without losing your mind madness and black radical creativity by lamar jarell bruce and
read by leon nixon who is doing his thing okay but i'm listening to this book have we been saying
you know if you cage a man they'll lose it if you cage your people they're gonna flip out
in regards to the people of gessa it's actually absolutely sane absolutely sane
to buck up when folks have been caging you so let's not say that no more it's absolutely sane
that when you have been imprisoned the way folks have been in the united states shout out to the
brothers who are striking in alabama that you would buck up it's absolutely sane
so go listen read whatever you need to do with this it's brilliant and necessary and it makes you go
hold up i'm not crazy i'm actually very sane because you mofos is crazy for trying to lock us down